{"qid": "easy-yelp-0000", "question": "What is the address of Snip Philadelphia in area with postal code 19130?", "answer": "2052 Fairmount Ave"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0001", "question": "What is the address of Smilies in area with postal code T5V 1H9?", "answer": "15003 118 Ave"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0002", "question": "What is the address of Cutting Edge Upholstery Solutions in area with postal code 33611?", "answer": "4338 S Manhattan Ave"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0003", "question": "What is the address of FedEx Office Print & Ship Center in area with postal code 33612?", "answer": "2798 E Fowler Ave"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0004", "question": "What is the address of Walmart Supercenter in area with postal code 37211?", "answer": "5824 Nolensville Pike, 4040 Nolensville Pike"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0005", "question": "What is the address of Level Seven Salon in area with postal code 19460?", "answer": "427 Schuylkill Rd"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0006", "question": "What is the address of Legacy Park Apartments in area with postal code 46112?", "answer": "6750 Legacy Park Dr"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0007", "question": "What is the address of Domino's Pizza in area with postal code 08103?", "answer": "446 S Broadway"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0008", "question": "What is the address of Best Auto Detailz in area with postal code T6B 3C5?", "answer": "6916 68 Avenue NW"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0009", "question": "What is the address of 7-Eleven in area with postal code 37203?", "answer": "3400 West End Ave"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0010", "question": "Which city is Ali Baba Cafe & Hookah Bar located in PA?", "answer": "Philadelphia"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0011", "question": "Which city is The Pink Daisy located in PA?", "answer": "Yardley"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0012", "question": "Which city is Mi Hacienda Mexican Restaurant located in IN?", "answer": "Carmel"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0013", "question": "Which city is Guild Mortgage Company located in ID?", "answer": "Eagle"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0014", "question": "Which city is Riverview Restaurant & Marina located in TN?", "answer": "Ashland City"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0015", "question": "Which city is Famous Tate Appliance & Bedding Center located in FL?", "answer": "Lutz, Wesley Chapel, Largo, Tampa, Brandon, Spring Hill, Port Richey, Oldsmar"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0016", "question": "Which city is Knapp's Cyclery located in NJ?", "answer": "Trenton"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0017", "question": "Which city is Francis The Duke Barber Co. located in PA?", "answer": "Philadelphia"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0018", "question": "Which city is Whitewater Park Apartments located in ID?", "answer": "Boise"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0019", "question": "What state is Gelato Aromi located in?", "answer": "PA"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0020", "question": "What state is America Bar & Grill located in?", "answer": "PA"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0021", "question": "What state is Plumber of Tucson located in?", "answer": "AZ"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0022", "question": "What state is Luna Hair located in?", "answer": "PA"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0023", "question": "What state is Sun Ray Grill located in?", "answer": "LA"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0024", "question": "What state is China Bowl Restaurant located in?", "answer": "PA"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0025", "question": "What state is Fence USA located in?", "answer": "NJ"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0026", "question": "What state is Nonno's Bakery located in?", "answer": "PA"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0027", "question": "What state is Schweiger Dermatology Group located in?", "answer": "PA"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0028", "question": "What is the postal code of Ceviche Tapas Bar & Restaurant in Clearwater, FL?", "answer": "33759"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0029", "question": "What is the postal code of Josette Tkacik in Santa Barbara, CA?", "answer": "93101"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0030", "question": "What is the postal code of Vogue Nails in Somerdale, NJ?", "answer": "08083"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0031", "question": "What is the postal code of Arby's in Troy, IL?", "answer": "62294"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0032", "question": "What is the postal code of Snoozy's Cafe in Schwenksville, PA?", "answer": "19473"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0033", "question": "What is the postal code of ITT Technical Institute in Indianapolis, IN?", "answer": "46268"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0034", "question": "What is the postal code of Cynergy Tax in Christiana, DE?", "answer": "19702"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0035", "question": "What is the postal code of J & S Mechanical in Hendersonville, TN?", "answer": "37075"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0036", "question": "What is the postal code of China in Bombay in Ballwin, MO?", "answer": "63011"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0037", "question": "What is the star rating of Ent Specialists in area with postal code 89502, Reno, NV?", "answer": "3.5"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0038", "question": "What is the star rating of Homeward Bound Veterinary Services in area with postal code 89523, Reno, NV?", "answer": "5.0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0039", "question": "What is the star rating of Perenn Bakery in area with postal code 89511, Reno, NV?", "answer": "4.5"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0040", "question": "What is the star rating of Hermann London Real Estate Group in area with postal code 63143, St. Louis, MO?", "answer": "3.0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0041", "question": "What is the star rating of Rural King in area with postal code 62226, Swansea, IL?", "answer": "2.5"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0042", "question": "What is the star rating of Red Mango in area with postal code 19153, Philadelphia, PA?", "answer": "3.0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0043", "question": "What is the star rating of The Scented Leaf in area with postal code 85701, Tucson, AZ?", "answer": "4.5"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0044", "question": "What is the star rating of The Home Depot in area with postal code 08081, Sicklerville, NJ?", "answer": "2.0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0045", "question": "What is the star rating of Golden Donut in area with postal code 19147, Philadelphia, PA?", "answer": "3.5"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0046", "question": "How many reviews does South Shore Dental Excellence receive in the area with postal code 33534, Gibsonton, FL, received?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0047", "question": "How many reviews does Le Onde Ristorante receive in the area with postal code 19027, Elkins Park, PA, received?", "answer": "19"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0048", "question": "How many reviews does Las Cebollas Mexican Grill receive in the area with postal code 37115, Madison, TN, received?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0049", "question": "How many reviews does Fifth Street Deli & Market receive in the area with postal code 85711, Tucson, AZ, received?", "answer": "86"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0050", "question": "How many reviews does Number 1 Beauty Supply receive in the area with postal code 19143, Philadelphia, PA, received?", "answer": "7"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0051", "question": "How many reviews does Goodyear Auto Service receive in the area with postal code 34683, Palm Harbor, FL, received?", "answer": "10"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0052", "question": "How many reviews does Iron Hill Brewery TapHouse receive in the area with postal code 19341, Exton, PA, received?", "answer": "41"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0053", "question": "How many reviews does Cherokee Store receive in the area with postal code 33611, Tampa, FL, received?", "answer": "9"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0054", "question": "How many reviews does Cool Springs Family Medicine receive in the area with postal code 37067, Franklin, TN, received?", "answer": "29"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0055", "question": "Is Melodies Cafe still open in area with postal code 19003, Ardmore, PA?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0056", "question": "Is Potter Family Eye Care still open in area with postal code 46055, McCordsville, IN?", "answer": "Yes"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0057", "question": "Is Denny's still open in area with postal code T6L 7A7, Edmonton, AB?", "answer": "Yes"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0058", "question": "Is Einstein Bros. Bagels still open in area with postal code 33609, Tampa, FL?", "answer": "Yes"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0059", "question": "Is Westampton Family Diner still open in area with postal code 08060, Mount Holly, NJ?", "answer": "Yes"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0060", "question": "Is The Farmacy NJ still open in area with postal code 08065, Palmyra, NJ?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0061", "question": "Is Saigon Noodle Bar still open in area with postal code 19118, Philadelphia, PA?", "answer": "Yes"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0062", "question": "Is A & D Automotive Center still open in area with postal code 33602, Tampa, FL?", "answer": "Yes"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0063", "question": "Is William Whitfield Park still open in area with postal code 37211, Nashville, TN?", "answer": "Yes"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0064", "question": "Does Mayuri Indian Restaurant require appointment in area with postal code 33617, Tampa, FL?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0065", "question": "Does Tequila Sunrise require appointment in area with postal code 46038, Fishers, IN?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0066", "question": "Does Nordvind Resort require appointment in area with postal code 33706, Treasure Is, FL?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0067", "question": "Does Santa Barbara Brewery Tours require appointment in area with postal code 93101, Santa Barbara, CA?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0068", "question": "Does Mi Jalapeno require appointment in area with postal code 62269, O'Fallon, IL?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0069", "question": "Does Franklin's Classic Steaks & Hoagies require appointment in area with postal code 19468, Limerick, PA?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0070", "question": "Does Dentists On Washington require appointment in area with postal code 19147, Philadelphia, PA?", "answer": "Yes"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0071", "question": "Does Sonny's BBQ require appointment in area with postal code 33543, Wesley Chapel, FL?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0072", "question": "Does Philippine Smoked BBQ Grill require appointment in area with postal code 19805, Wilmington, DE?", "answer": "No"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0073", "question": "What are the hours of operation for Panera Bread in area with postal code 33566, Plant City, FL?", "answer": "Monday: 7:0-20:30, Tuesday: 7:0-20:30, Wednesday: 7:0-20:30, Thursday: 7:0-20:30, Friday: 7:0-20:30, Saturday: 7:0-20:30, Sunday: 7:0-20:30"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0074", "question": "What are the hours of operation for Smoothie King in area with postal code 33781, Pinellas Park, FL?", "answer": "Monday: 0:0-0:0, Tuesday: 7:0-21:0, Wednesday: 7:0-19:0, Thursday: 10:0-16:0, Friday: 7:0-19:0, Saturday: 9:0-20:0, Sunday: 11:0-18:0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0075", "question": "What are the hours of operation for K9 Athletic Club in area with postal code 63110, Saint Louis, MO?", "answer": "Monday: 6:30-18:30, Tuesday: 6:30-18:30, Wednesday: 6:30-18:30, Thursday: 6:30-18:30, Friday: 6:30-18:30, Saturday: 9:0-17:0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0076", "question": "What are the hours of operation for Ms Goody Cupcake in area with postal code 19148, Philadelphia, PA?", "answer": "Tuesday: 11:0-19:0, Wednesday: 11:0-19:0, Thursday: 11:0-19:0, Friday: 11:0-21:0, Saturday: 11:0-21:0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0077", "question": "What are the hours of operation for Briggs Auction in area with postal code 19060, Garnet Valley, PA?", "answer": "Thursday: 16:0-19:0, Friday: 9:0-23:0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0078", "question": "What are the hours of operation for Ocean Breeze Cleaning and Handyman Service in area with postal code 89434, Sparks, NV?", "answer": "Monday: 0:0-0:0, Tuesday: 7:0-17:0, Wednesday: 7:0-17:0, Thursday: 7:0-12:0, Friday: 7:0-12:0, Saturday: 7:0-12:0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0079", "question": "What are the hours of operation for Pennsylvania Soup & Seafood House in area with postal code 18901, Doylestown, PA?", "answer": "Monday: 11:0-15:0, Tuesday: 11:0-15:0, Wednesday: 11:0-20:0, Thursday: 11:0-19:0, Friday: 11:0-20:0, Saturday: 11:0-20:0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0080", "question": "What are the hours of operation for Jimmy John's in area with postal code 62269, O'Fallon, IL?", "answer": "Monday: 11:0-22:0, Tuesday: 11:0-22:0, Wednesday: 11:0-22:0, Thursday: 11:0-22:0, Friday: 11:0-22:0, Saturday: 11:0-22:0, Sunday: 11:0-22:0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0081", "question": "What are the hours of operation for Chef JJ's Back Yard in area with postal code 46220, Indianapolis, IN?", "answer": "Monday: 0:0-0:0, Tuesday: 12:0-18:0, Wednesday: 12:0-18:0, Thursday: 12:0-18:0, Friday: 12:0-18:0, Saturday: 12:0-17:0"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0082", "question": "What categories does The Piper Pub & Grill belong to, in area with postal code 83702, Boise, ID?", "answer": "Nightlife, Pubs, Bars, American (Traditional), Restaurants"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0083", "question": "What categories does Clemens Chimney Sweep belong to, in area with postal code 19053, Feasterville Trevose, PA?", "answer": "Chimney Sweeps, Home Services, Masonry/Concrete, Contractors"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0084", "question": "What categories does Two Men and a Truck St. Louis East belong to, in area with postal code 62234, Collinsville, IL?", "answer": "Home Services, Movers, Shopping, Packing Services, Packing Supplies"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0085", "question": "What categories does Tacos Jalisco belong to, in area with postal code 89502, Reno, NV?", "answer": "Mexican, Restaurants"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0086", "question": "What categories does Sandbar Patio Bar & Grill belong to, in area with postal code 83714, Boise, ID?", "answer": "Food, Restaurants, American (Traditional)"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0087", "question": "What categories does Buddy's Burgers - Kennett Square belong to, in area with postal code 19348, Kennett Square, PA?", "answer": "Burgers, Fast Food, Restaurants"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0088", "question": "What categories does Highway Tire & Auto Service belong to, in area with postal code 08060, Mount Holly, NJ?", "answer": "Tires, Towing, Automotive, Oil Change Stations, Auto Repair"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0089", "question": "What categories does Baily's Dairy belong to, in area with postal code 19382, West Chester, PA?", "answer": "Food, Specialty Food"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0090", "question": "What categories does Orvelle Nails & Spa belong to, in area with postal code 37027, Brentwood, TN?", "answer": "Beauty & Spas, Nail Salons"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0091", "question": "What are the coordinates of Holiday Inn Express Nashville W I40/Whitebridge Rd in area with postal code 37209, Nashville, TN?", "answer": "36.1484039504, -86.8590614945"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0092", "question": "What are the coordinates of Kary's Beauty Salon in area with postal code 19148, Philadelphia, PA?", "answer": "39.9288599, -75.1566897"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0093", "question": "What are the coordinates of Ada County in area with postal code 83704, Boise, ID?", "answer": "43.6089445, -116.2873523"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0094", "question": "What are the coordinates of Chal-Brit Beverages in area with postal code 18914, Chalfont, PA?", "answer": "40.2893931, -75.1994282"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0095", "question": "What are the coordinates of Italian Bistro in area with postal code 19152, Philadelphia, PA?", "answer": "40.0731939, -75.0352627"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0096", "question": "What are the coordinates of D & B Tailors in area with postal code 19073, Newtown Square, PA?", "answer": "39.9875334, -75.4001299"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0097", "question": "What are the coordinates of Zachs Famous Donair in area with postal code T6K 3L6, Edmonton, AB?", "answer": "53.4722697, -113.4504354"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0098", "question": "What are the coordinates of Nicholson Cleaners in area with postal code 37203, Nashville, TN?", "answer": "36.1483514, -86.8079997"}
{"qid": "easy-yelp-0099", "question": "What are the coordinates of NTB-National Tire & Battery in area with postal code 37027, Brentwood, TN?", "answer": "35.9617839364, -86.8168482184"}
